// questions
var questions = [
  {
    question: "What kind of operator is && (and)?",
    answers: [
      "Arithmetic ",
      "Logical",
      "Mechanical",
      "Comparison"],
    correctAnswer: 1,
  },
  {
    question: "What does a confirm method do?",
    answers: [
      "Displays a box with a message",
      "Runs a function",
      "Asks the user to enter a value",
      "Asks the user to confirm an action"
    ],
    correctAnswer: 3,
  },
  {
    question: "Which of these is a primitive data type?",
    answers: [
      "String",
      "Object",
      "If statement",
      "Variable"
    ],
    correctAnswer: 0,
  },
  {
    question: "How many expressions can a for loop take in the parentheses?",
    answers: [
      "One",
      "Three",
      "Seven",
      "Ten"
    ],
    correctAnswer: 1,
  },
  {
    question: "What kind of brackets are used when declaring objects?",
    answers: [
      "Curly {}",
      "Parentheses ()",
      "Square []",
      "Brackets aren't used"
    ],
    correctAnswer: 0,
  },
  {
    question: "How would you display a message in the console?",
    answers: [
      "// display message",
      "alert('display message');",
      "console.log('display message');",
      "console = 'display message';"
    ],
    correctAnswer: 2,
  },
  {
    question: "Which code below will save to localStorage?",
    answers: [
      "localStorage = 'key' + 'value';",
      "localStorage.getItem(key, value);",
      "localStorage.setItem(key, value);",
      "setItem(localStorage, key, value);"
    ],
    correctAnswer: 2,
  },
  {
    question: "How do you access indices of an array?",
    answers: [
      "Dot notation - MyArray.2",
      "Square brackets - MyArray[2]",
      "Ampersands - MyArray&&2",
      "Equals symbol - MyArray = 2"
    ],
    correctAnswer: 1,
  },
  {
    question: "Whats the difference between using == and === when comparing two values?",
    answers: [
      "Using === is better than using == because there's more of them",
      "== compares the values and types, === compares the values only",
      "They are not used, only = is used to compare values",
      "== compares the values only, === compares the values and types"
    ],
    correctAnswer: 3,
  },
  {
    question: "What would myVariable++ do?",
    answers: [
      "Add 1 to myVariable",
      "Make a copy of myVariable",
      "Doubles the value of myVariable",
      "Makes myVariable equal to 0"
    ],
    correctAnswer: 0,
  }
];
